<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="10"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Audio



                  &



             Quiz














                    Written and illustrated by :
                                                         Sarra Ben Amara]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Once  upon  a  time,  in  a  dense  forest,  there  lived  a


    clever  little  fox  named  Felix.  Felix  was  known  for  his



    sharp  mind  and  keen  observation  skills.  He  loved


    exploring  the  forest  and  learning  new  things  every



    day.]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[One sunny morning, Felix saw a squirrel struggling to


     reach  a  high  branch  to  gather  some  acorns.  Felix



     quickly  thought  of  a  plan  and  gathered  some  fallen


     branches  to  make  a  small  ladder.  The  squirrel  was



     grateful and thanked Felix for his clever idea.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[after that day, Felix heard a commotion near the river.


    A  group  of  animals  was  arguing  about  how  to  cross


    the  river  safely.  Some  suggested  swimming,  while



    others  thought  of  building  a  raft.  Felix  quietly



    observed the situation and noticed a fallen tree lying


    across the river. He pointed it out to the animals, who


    then used it as a bridge to cross safely.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Felix's ability to observe and think before acting made


   him a valuable friend to all the animals in the forest.



   He  never  boasted  about  his  cleverness  but  always


   used it to help others.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[As  days  passed,  Felix  continued  to  help  his  friends


     and  learned  something  new  every  day.  He  watched


     the birds build their nests, the ants work together to



     gather  food,  and  the  bees  create  honeycombs.  The



     more he observed, the wiser he became.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Remember














                       Take time to observe and think




                       before acting. Helping others



                       and using your intelligence



                       wisely can make a big




                       difference.]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Join Felix, the clever little fox, on his adventures in the forest!



                    Felix uses his sharp mind to help his friends, like building a ladder for a squirrel and



                    finding a bridge to cross a river. This heartwarming tale shows how wisdom and




                                                  kindness can make a big difference.



                      Perfect for young readers, "The Clever Little Fox" is a delightful story about



                                                      friendship and clever thinking.








                                                            Click me When


                                                               you’re ready

























                                                 © 2024 Sarra Ben Amara. All rights reserved..]]></page></pages></Search>